{
    "subject": "resource/Dilip_P._Gaonkar",
    "predicate": "property/workInstitutions",
    "object": "resource/Northwestern_University",
    "human_readable": "Dilip P. Gaonkar worked at Northwestern University.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9886765480041504,
            "question": "Has Dilip P. Gaonkar worked at Northwestern University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9785370826721191,
            "question": "Is Dilip P. Gaonkar affiliated with Northwestern University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9745782017707825,
            "question": "Name a university where Dilip P. Gaonkar has worked."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9113056659698486,
            "question": "Where did Dilip P. Gaonkar work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8694931268692017,
            "question": "What is the name of the university that employed Dilip P. Gaonkar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8342427015304565,
            "question": "Who is Dilip P. Gaonkar and where did he work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8275084495544434,
            "question": "What university was associated with Dilip P. Gaonkar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7906411290168762,
            "question": "At which institution did Dilip P. Gaonkar hold a position?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6363463401794434,
            "question": "What is known about Dilip P. Gaonkar's work history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6229925751686096,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Dilip P. Gaonkar's professional affiliations?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dilip P. Gaonkar worked at Northwestern University.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4605_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about Dilip P. Gaonkar's work history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4605_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=At which institution did Dilip P. Gaonkar hold a position?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4605_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What university was associated with Dilip P. Gaonkar?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4605_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4605_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4605_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4605_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4605_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4605_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4605_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4605_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4605_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4605_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4605_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently indicate that Dilip Parameshwar Gaonkar is a Professor at Northwestern University in various capacities, including being the Director of Center for Global Culture and Communication and Director of Center for Transcultural Studies there. This supports the statement that Dilip P. Gaonkar worked at Northwestern University."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}